<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>seminars on IIGB Bioinformatics Core @ UCR</title>
    <link>https://iigb-bioinfocore.github.io/tags/seminars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in seminars on IIGB Bioinformatics Core @ UCR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iigb-bioinfocore.github.io/tags/seminars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Single Cell Core Grant Program</title>
      <link>https://iigb-bioinfocore.github.io/blog/2022/09/22/single-cell-grant-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iigb-bioinfocore.github.io/blog/2022/09/22/single-cell-grant-program/</guid>
      <description>Info An informational hybrid in-person/webinar on a single cell core grant program hosted by the IIGB Genomics and Bioinformatics Cores, Parse Biosciences, and Illumina.
The session provides information on the split-pool combinatorial barcoding technology developed at Parse Biosciences and a grant program involving the IIGB cores, Parse Biosciences, and Illumina. Here short talks by:
 Wei Zhang (Genomics Coordinator) Brandon Le (Bioinformatics Coordinator) Bo Liu (Executive Sales Specialist, Illumina) John Walsh (VP Marketing, Parse Biosciences) Samantha O&amp;rsquo;Neill (Technical Sales Manager, Parse Biosciences)  Come learn more about how to apply for the award.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parse Biosciences Seminar</title>
      <link>https://iigb-bioinfocore.github.io/blog/2022/02/24/parse-biosciences-seminar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 10:00:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iigb-bioinfocore.github.io/blog/2022/02/24/parse-biosciences-seminar/</guid>
      <description>UCR Institute for Integrative Genome Biology hosts a seminar by Parse Biosciences titled &amp;ldquo;Single Cell 3.0 - The Next Evolution of Single Cell Genomics&amp;rdquo;.
Scalable single-cell RNA sequencing (scRNA-seq) up to 1 MILLION cells is readily available with the Evercode technology. The core of this approach, split-pool combinatorial barcoding, was originally demonstrated in a 2018 Science paper with SPLiT-seq and substantially improved for wide-scale adoption.
Our speakers will describe the Evercode technology, its implication on single-cell experiments, and the drastic improvements achieved since the original publication.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
